Hello there!
Welcome to my lesson.
I saw that you are having a bad, bad period in classroom.
You never listen to me.
So today I wanna try a new kind of teaching.
Are you ready?
Okay.
Are you alone at home?
Yes?
Perfect.
now follow my instruction this is going to be a fun online lesson
okay
take out your cook
yes like this
good boy
what a beautiful cock
okay let's start start stroking it
yes like this nice and softly
yes
what a good boy
massage your balls baby
yes like this
now up and down
good boy listen to me
yes baby massage your balls for me
very big balls
but keep calm I don't want to make you explode
oh wow
you have a beautiful cook baby yes
fast baby fast
yes like this
now slowly, softly
good boy
Jerking baby, yes.
Jerking fast.
Oh.
You are a really good student.
Wow.
Oh.
I know you want to explode now your teacher wants you to start a jerk it harder yes like this
fast baby fast
listen to me
Jack in the harbour, yes.
Okay, you are ready.
You are ready to explode.
Okay.
Five, four, three, two.
one
oh yes
oh
good boy
wow
you are a good student
see you soon